(Sheldon:)and then to cap off the perfect day,
(Sheldon:)the Los Angeles Bureau
of Weights and Measures.
(Leonard:)I thought the measures were
going to be the stars of the show.
(Leonard:)Turns out it was the weights.
(Penny:)I'm so glad you guys
are friends again.
(Sheldon:)And I'm glad you and I
are friends again, too.
(Sheldon:)Which reminds me. This came in the
mail, and I want you to have it.
"Fifty cents off Vagisil."
(Sheldon:)Think of me when you apply it.
(Raj:)Can I just say, I've missed
all of us hanging out together.
(Penny:)-Yeah.
-Me too.
Um, since when can Kcothrappali talk
in front of the girls without a beer?
(Bernadette:)Oh, that happened
right after you left.
(Leonard:)And no one told me?
(Howard(crying):)Can't believe we forgot to tell him.
Ahem. Think of Sheldon
when you apply it.